vebnest.com 2014-02-09

# Master Reseller Hosting | Alpha Reseller Host | Unlimited Reseller Hosting | Cheap | VPS | Dedicated Servers

By accessing or using the VEBNEST web site, you agree to the terms of the VEBNEST Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. VEBNEST reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Privacy Policy at the time of such use.

**Collection of personal information**  
When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering products, downloading software, or entering contests, VEBNEST may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, VEBNEST may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.  
In the process of administering our site, we maintain and track usage through Web server logs. Web server logs provide such information as what types of browsers are accessing our site, what pages receive high traffic, and the times of day our servers experience significant load. We use this information to improve the content and navigation features of our site. It is not used to personally identify you.

**How your personal information is used**  
VEBNEST collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. The information that you provide is also used as part of our effort to keep you informed about special offers and other products and services of VEBNEST and selected third parties.

**How we share your personal information**  
We will not sell, rent or lease to others telephone numbers or e-mail addresses. We will share the personal data you provide only with other VEBNEST entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above, except as provided below (see Consent).

**Consent**  
VEBNEST will use and share the personally identifiable information you provided to us in ways related to those described above. We reserve the right to disclose any and all pertinent customer information to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.

**Reprinting personal information**  
Please note that any information you post to a public bulletin board or chat room, is available to all persons accessing that site.

**Abuse Reports**  
We know for having lots of scam and fraudulant activities, most of the hosted customers face several unconscious abuse report(s). We therefore, tried to create a powerful abuse team to verify the abuse reports (Copyright, Email Spam, Unauthorised Activities) sent to us. We first verify the reporters identity and then verify the existence of copyrighted material according to our company law. A reporter has to send a paper with the compnay header signed by him/her/company’s MD to prove the copyright authorisation. According to MLA, only Abuse Department (Or Piracy Department) of the related company/personal is only allowed to send an abuse request to our Department for verification. If its a personal copyright, then a Passport identity including his/her copyright over the material has to be proven to our abuse department. All the documents are verified according to our law and MLA. If Abuse passes the request to Support, then support department asks the owner to take proper action against the complaint. If support doesn’t receive proper information(s) from client then a suspention is issued after 15 days of escalation. This steps are only taken to prevent fradulant scam reports and reduce the activities of support to verify the abuse report. For Email spamming a proper header is required so that its possible to do a network scan and find out the verification of the email sender. For any Abuse report please contact our Abuse department using the contact provided here: http://www.vebnest.com/contact.php

**Privacy related concerns**  
Should you have questions or concerns relating to this Privacy Statement or compliance with it, please send e-mail to: sales@vebnest.com
